woodnet.net 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - August Home Publishing Company

## Privacy Policy

August Home Publishing Company (“August Home”) is committed to respecting your privacy. Please read the following to understand how your personal information will be treated. By using August Home’s web site and other related web sites and services that display or link to this policy (collectively, the “web site”), you are agreeing to the terms of the August Home Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This policy will let you know the following: 

  1. How does August Home collect and use my e-mail address?
  2. How do I stop receiving e-mails from August Home?
  3. How does August Home collect and use telephone numbers and street addresses?
  4. How can I stop receiving telephone calls or mailings from August Home or third parties?
  5. Can I be identified when I browse the web site?
  6. What is August Home’s policy on collecting information from children?
  7. What is August Home’s relationship to third parties and other web sites?

####  1\. How does August Home collect and use my e-mail address? 

E-mail addresses may be collected when you subscribe to one of our magazines. We will use your e-mail address to contact you when it is time to renew your subscription and to send you information on August Home products or services. We do not currently rent, sell or give email addresses to any third party; however, in the future, we may rent only those email addresses collected from magazine subscriptions to reputable third parties who wish to promote their products or services to you via e-mail. 

When ordering a gift subscription, you are given the option of providing the recipient’s e-mail address for August Home to notify him or her of their gift subscription. Unless the gift recipient chooses in the future to provide August Home with his or her e-mail address, recipients will be contacted via e-mail for gift notification purposes only and will not receive any further electronic correspondence from August Home or third parties. 

We also collect your e-mail address in a variety of other circumstances including, but not limited to, when you sign up to receive e-mail tips, take part in a survey, participate in a forum, order a product or sign up to receive electronic information or other value added content available through purchase of a special interest book. We will contact you via e-mail, depending on the circumstances which you had provided your e-mail address. For example, we may contact you to send you e-mail tips, to notify you if you are a winner of an online contest, to confirm your identity as part of a forum, to e-mail you a lost password or user i.d., to answer a question you have about a product you ordered or to notify you if a product you ordered is out of stock, or if requested, to provide shipping quotes. Personally identifiable information will be collected from registrants of the various online forums provided by August Home as a service to users of the website (the “Forums”). Forum registrants will be asked to provide a login name, a display name and email address. This information will be used to create a registration account, which will be protected by a password of user’s choosing. Users are responsible for taking all reasonable steps to ensure that no unauthorized person has access to the user’s Forum account and password. Users are solely responsible for: (1) controlling the dissemination and use of the user’s display name, and password; (2) authorizing, monitoring and controlling access to and use of the user’s Forum display name and password; and (3) promptly informing August Home of any need to deactivate a password. 

In order to keep you up-to-date on the services and products offered by August Home, we may occasionally contact you via e-mail to alert you of specific offers, products or services that we feel may be of interest to you. We will not, unless otherwise indicated in this privacy policy, rent, sell or give your e-mail address to any third party. 

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has established business relationships, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To make such a request, please write to us at the address for August Home Publishing Company Customer Service as set forth in Section 2 below. 

####  2\. How do I stop receiving e-mails from August Home? 

Anytime you receive an e-mail offering a product or service from August Home and you wish to stop receiving or unsubscribe from any similar e-mails, you may either (1) click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each e-mail or (2) contact August Home Customer Service as set forth below. Our business hours are Monday through Friday, 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. Central Standard Time. 

> Toll-Free E-mail Customer Service Line: 1-866-553-7514  
>  August Home Publishing Company Customer Service  
>  2200 Grand Avenue  
>  Des Moines, IA 50312  
>  E-mail: [orders@augusthome.com](mailto:orders@augusthome.com)

You may call the Toll-Free E-mail Customer Service Line to discuss with a representative which types of e-mails you are currently receiving from August Home and specify which e-mail list(s) you would like to remain on and which you would like to be removed from. 

If you subscribe to an August Home magazine, and do not want August Home to contact you regarding renewal of your subscription, or to receive August Home products or services or be contacted by a third party, you may opt out of receiving such communication by visiting the customer service link accessible from any one of our magazine home pages. 

####  3\. How does August Home collect and use telephone numbers and street addresses? 

We collect telephone numbers and street addresses in certain circumstances including, but not limited to, when customers purchase a product for themselves or others from one of August Home’s e-commerce web sites or order a subscription for themselves or others to one of our magazines. We will use customers’ street addresses to fulfill orders or magazine subscriptions. We or one of our business partners working on our behalf may use customers’ street addresses and/or telephone numbers to contact them if there is a question about an order, if something is out of stock or to notify a customer when it is time to renew his or her subscription. In order to keep customers up-to-date on the services and products offered by August Home, we may occasionally use our customers’ street addresses and/or telephone numbers to alert them of specific August Home offers, products or services that we feel may be of interest to them. As a subscriber, our customers’ street addresses and/or telephone numbers may be rented to reputable third parties who wish to promote their product or service. 

####  4\. How can I stop receiving telephone calls or mailings from August Home or third parties? 

Please contact August Home Customer Service at the above telephone number or address if you do not want us to contact you regarding renewal of your magazine subscription or to receive August Home products or services. You may also contact August Home Customer Service if you do not want us to share your street address or telephone number with third parties. 

####  5\. Can I be identified when I browse the web site? 

In general, you can browse this web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We are, however, able to determine your internet service provider’s (ISP) address and domain name (i.e. aol.com, hotmail.com, etc.). We use this information to help administer this web site, to measure the use of the web site and to improve the content of the web site. So we know where, in a general sense, our visitors are coming from, but we do not know who you are unless you tell us by filling out a form. 

Notwithstanding, August Home does research on our users’ demographics, interest and behavior based on the information provided to us while browsing the web site. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. August Home may share this aggregated data with others. 

Additionally, some of our web pages may contain cookies, which are tiny data files that are sent to your web browser and stored on your computer. This allows our web server to recognize you when you visit the web site in the future. Most web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent. If you choose not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features of the web site that are available to other visitors. 

####  6\. What is August Home’s policy on collecting information from children? 

August Home’s web sites are not directed toward children and August Home does not intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without the permission of the child’s parent or legal guardian. Children under the age of 13 should submit personally identifiable information to August Home only with the explicit permission of their parent or legal guardian. If your child has submitted personal information and you would like that information to be removed from our database, you may contact August Home as indicated above and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. 

####  7\. What is August Home’s relationship to third parties or other web sites? 

To make the web site more useful to our users, we may offer some features in conjunction with third party providers that specialize in operating such services. For example, if you choose to subscribe to one of our magazines through our web site, we may forward your information to a third party for services such as credit card processing and order fulfillment. When you purchase a product through our web site, the information you provide about yourself may also be forwarded to other sites which are managed or operated by third parties. Third party internet sites and services accessible through the August Home web site have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent from us. August Home has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. 

In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by August Home or any parent subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, information from or about web site users may be among the transferred assets. 

Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, August Home cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process and you do so at your own risk. 

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, you may contact us at the above address or send an e-mail to [orders@augusthome.com](mailto:orders@augusthome.com).
